I'm Cole Davis. I am the founder and CEO
of SwitchCord. I'm a lawyer and
technologist and I spoke today on what do
we call it? Contract credentials and
verifiable legal authority. So modeling
legal relationships stuck in paper-based
agreements, PDFs, Word documents into
KERI, ACDC spec to be proving your
contractual authority to third parties. So
I see things differently now after living
in this world for the past six, seven
years. That contractual authority and your
ability to go through life and do things
depends on legal contracts and authority
from the state and you can't get away from
it. And so I stopped viewing these things
as separate and it's all sort of this
interrelated mix of identity and legal.
And that led to me also seeing finance
accounting, legal finance and accounting
is not separate disciplines like I was
taught and have degrees in, but it's
really a spectrum. And identity, I found,
is the one thing that ties all of them to
together. It is the backbone of commercial
transactions. And I think people are
starting to come around to that idea. I've
been saying it for a long time and it's
exciting to see people, their eyes light
up when they realize what I'm talking
about. So if my work and research were to
just disappear, I think it would be I've
been working to push this society towards
Ronald Koest's magical world of zero
transaction costs. So I'm using identity
and AI and every tool at my disposal to
reduce the cost of doing commercial
transactions to bring shared economic
prosperity. If it were to go away, I think
we'd be stuck with centralized databases,
centralized processes that don't scale and
are not they're beholden to the existing
gatekeepers and it does not allow us to
push forward as a society. Thank you.